## **Profile**

A fourth year Interactive Art and Technology student strives to create and improve interaction and digital experience through human-centred designs. Passionated about create designs that are aesthetically pleasing and commercially viable, aligning user experience with business goals.

### Skills

### Design

## Experience Design Interaction Design Interface Design Visual Branding Sketching

### **Process**

| User Research | Photoshop         |
|---------------|-------------------|
| Ideation      | Adobe Illustrator |
| Wireframing   | InDesign          |
| Prototyping   | Figma             |
| Testing       | Adobe XD          |

# Academic Experience

## Bandsintown Amplify

User Experience Design Course

Oct - Dec 2024

 Prototyped Bandsintown's new digital platform for local music artists and venues to connect together and schedule performances using Figma and created promotion video using After Effects.

**Tools** 

- Assisted in 4 user interviews with current local music artists through Zoom to discover possible touchpoint for the digital experience.
- Led the visuals and interaction for the platform, leveraging user data and academic research to guide the project in the optimal direction.

## Heritage Burnaby Interactive Map

Interaction Design Course

Sept - Dec 2023

- Collaborated with Heritage Burnaby's curator to redesign their outdated interactive map with a community story-sharing feature, addressing client and user needs.
- Synthesized user research into personas, journey maps, and storyboards to better understand user needs and frame problem space.
- Designed activities to engage user testing participants in contributing their thoughts to the design concepts.
- Built mid-fidelity interactive prototypes for user flow and client-side in Figma.

#### **SafeNomads**

Interface Design Course

May - August 2022

- Conceptualized and developed a user-friendly mobile application prototype with 2 different user flows in Figma and Protopie to assist solo travellers in securing their safety.
- Conducted on-site interviews with 8 solo travellers to find their goals and challenges.
- Facilitated 4 usability testing sessions with current and prospective solo travellers.

236. 979. 9718



# Work Experience

# Freelance Multimedia Designer

Saltus Grammar School

April 2023 - Present

- Producing a wide range of visual graphics for school use, including promotional materials, presentations, social media content, and annual campaigns using Adobe Creative Suite (InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightroom).
- Effectively communicating with the Director of Marketing in a remote work setting to ensure alignment on design objectives, project timelines, and brand consistency.

# Graphic Designer (Co-op)

York House School

Sept 2022 - April 2023

- Designed over 100 materials for students and teachers, ensuring professionalism in a school setting and adherence to the brand guidelines.
- Created website banners for the school's landing page and event pages, and customized digital mail buttons to fit various email settings.
- Communicated with printing services to get printing proofs for brochures, magazines and secured printed marketing materials on time.

# Volunteer Experience

# Vice President of Design

Volunteer - SFU LYFE

July 2022 - May 2023

- Directed a team of one design coordinator and two social media coordinators to design marketing materials.
- Customized and optimized the club's website landing pages using Figma and Wordpress for specific event promotions.
- Designed graphics for the new social media's account based on the branding using Figma, which followed by 100+ followers on Instagram.

#### **Orientation Leader**

Volunteer - Fraser International College

September 2021

- Supported a group of 20 new college students to adapt to the new academic environment by organizing team-building activities.
- Led a campus tour to help new students find academic resources and support.

## **Education**

## Bachelor of Arts, Major in Interactive Arts and Technology Publishing Minor

Simon Fraser University

January 2021 - Expected graduation: June 2024